module.exports = [
	//1
	{
		question: '1',
		answer: '2'
	},
	//2
	{
		question: 'two',
		answer: 'three'
	},
	//3
	{
		question: 'iii',
		answer: 'iv'
	},
	//4
	{
		question: 'Thursday',
		answer: 'Friday'
	},
	//5
	{
		question: 'Empire Strikes Back',
		answer: 'Return of the Jedi'
	},
	//6
	{
		question: 'Half-Blood Prince',
		answer: 'Deathly Hallows'
	},
	//7
	{
		question: '111',
		answer: '1000'
	},
	//8
	{
		question: 'Honeycomb',
		answer: 'Ice Cream Sandwich'
	},
	//9
	{
		question: '23',
		answer: '29'
	},
	//10
	{
		question: 'John Tyler',
		answer: 'James Knox Polk'
	},
	//11
	{
		question: 'Matt Smith',
		answer: 'Peter Capaldi'
	}
];